Finding Aid for William Albright Papers 1962-1998
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Recordings
  - William Albright Works
    - Dream and Dance, for organ and percussion
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
    - The Dream Rags, for piano
      - [version 1], 3 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
    - Fantasy-Etudes for Saxophone Quartet, 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
    - Father, We Thank Thee: A song of thanksgiving for unison choir, soloist or congregation, with piano or organ accompaniment and optional instruments
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes digital audio tapes (Box 59)
      - [version 3], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 5], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 6], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
    - Five Chromatic Dances), 3 audiocassettes (Box 79)
    - Five Chromatic Dances (Box 59)
      - [versions 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [version 3], 1 audiocassettes digital audio tapes (Box 60)
      - [version 4], 1 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [version 5], 1 audiocassettes (Box 69)
      - [version 6], 6 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [versions 7-11], 5 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
      - [version 12], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 12], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 71)
      - [version 13-14], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 10 1/2" (Box 73)
      - [version 15-16], 4 reel-to-reel audiotapes 10 1/2" (Box 74)
    - Flights of Fancy: Ballet for Band, 1 audiocassettes (Box 60)
    - Flights of Fancy: Ballet for Organ
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes digital audio tapes (Box 60)
      - [version 3], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
        (AGO Fight Song only, taped with Bacchanal)
    - Foils for Wind Ensemble
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [versions 2-3], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
      - [version 5], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 6], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
        (taped with Carom)
    - Four Fancies for harpsichord
      - [versions 1-5], 5 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [version 6], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 7], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 71)
    - Frescos: Four Movements for Woodwind Quartet), 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
    - Full Moon in March
      - [versions 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [version 3], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
    - Gothic Suite for Organ, Strings and Percussion
      - [versions 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [version 3], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [version 5], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 5" (Box 69)
      - [version 6], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
      - [version 7], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
    - Grand Sonata in Rag, for piano, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
    - The Great Amen, for flute and piano
      - [versions 1-4], 3 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [version 5], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
        (taped with Abiding Passions)
      - [version 6], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
        (taped with Deo Gratias)
    - Halo, for large organ and metal instruments
      - [versions 1-2], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [version 3], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 71)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
    - Heater: Saga for solo alto saxophone and band
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 60)
        (taped with Foils)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 5" (Box 70)
      - [version 3], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [version 5], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [version 6], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 7], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
    - In memoriam, 1 audiocassettes (Box 60)
    - Introduction, Passacaglia and Rondo Capriccioso: A concerto for tack piano, seven winds and percussion
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [versions 3-4], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [versions 4-5], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
      - [versions 6-7], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 8], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
        (taped with Danse Macabre)
      - [version 9], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
    - Jericho: Battle music for organ and trumpet
      - [versions 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [versions 3-4], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
        (taped with Halo)
      - [version 5], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 6], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
    - Juba, for organ
      - [versions 1-2], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 3], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 5" (Box 78)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
      - [version 5], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
        (taped with Caroms)
      - [version 6], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
        (taped with Organbook I)
    - The King of Instruments: A parade of music and verse for organ and narrator
      - [versions 1-3], 3 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [version 4], 1 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [version 5], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [versions 6-8], 3 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
      - [version 9], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 10], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [versions 11-12], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 10 1/2" (Box 74)
      - [version 13-14], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 10 1/2" (Box 75)
    - Marcia Funebre (see Concerto for Harpsichord and String Orchestra) (Box 75)
    - Marginal Worlds, for 12 instruments
      - [version 1], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
        (taped with Juba)
    - Mass in D, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
    - Missa Brevis, for soprano or unison treble voices and organ (Box 70)
      - [versions 1-3], 3 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [version 4], 1 audiocassettes digital audio tapes (Box 60)
    - Organbook: A set of pieces for pipe organ
      - [versions 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [versions 3-4], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
        (tape part)
      - [version 5], 3 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 6], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
      - [versions 7-8], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
    - Organbook II
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 60)
        (taped ["Night Procession" only] with Gothic Suite)
      - [version 2-4], 3 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 5], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 6], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
        (taped with Dream and Dance)
      - [version 7], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
        ("Night Procession" only, taped with Halo)
      - [version 8], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
        (recital tape,taped with Organbook I)
      - [version 9], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 10 1/2" (Box 75)
    - Organbook III, 12 etudes for small organ
      - [versions 1-5], 5 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [version 6], 1 audiocassettes (Box 60)
        (taped with In memoriam)
      - [versions 7-8], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 9], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
    - Pax in Terra, mixed choir, a cappella with soprano and tenor soli
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 3], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 10 1/2" (Box 75)
    - Peace Pipe, for two bassoons
      - [version 1], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
    - Pianoagogo
      - [versions 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [version 3], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [versions 4-5], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 6], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [version 7], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [version 8], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [versions 9-10], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
      - [version 11], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
        (taped with Beulahland Rag)
      - [version 12], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 10 1/2" (Box 75)
    - Pit Band, for alto saxophone, bass clarinet and pianoforte
      - [versions 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [version 3], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
    - Pneuma, for organ
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 5" (Box 79)
      - [version 5], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
      - [version 6], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
    - Quintet for Clarinet and String Quartet
      - [versions 1-4], 3 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [version 5], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
        (taped with Antigone's Reply)
      - [version 6], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 7], 1 audiocassettes (Box 60)
        (taped with Pit Band)
      - [version 8], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 10 1/2" (Box 75)
      - [version 9], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 10 1/2" (Box 76)
    - Ragtime
      - [versions 1-3], 3 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
    - Romance, for french horn and organ
      - [version2 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [version 3], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
    - Rustles of Spring, 1994 for flute, alto saxophone, violin, violoncello, pianoforte
      - [versions 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [versions 3-4], 3 audiocassettes digital audio tapes (Box 60)
      - [version 5], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 6], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 7], 1 audiocassettes (Box 60)
    - Saints Preserve Us: Three "Etudes-prieres" for Solo Clarinet
      - [versions 1-2], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
    - Salvos: Music for Seven Players
      - [version 1], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
    - Seven Deadly Sins, for flute, clarinet, string quartet, piano, and optional narrator
      - [versions 1-6], 6 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 7], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
    - 1732 in memoriam Johannes Albrecht
      - [versions 1-7], 7 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [versions 8-9], 2 audiocassettes (Box 61)
    - Shadows, eight serenades for guitar
      - [versions 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 61)
      - [version 3], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 5], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 71)
    - Shepherd of All Who Inhabit the Earth
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 61)
        (taped with 1732)
    - Sleight of Hand Rag arrangement
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 61)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
    - Sonata for Alto Saxophone and Piano
      - [versions 1-8], 8 audiocassettes (Box 61)
    - Sonata for Oboe and Harpsichord, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 71)
    - A Song to David: for antiphonal choirs, soloists, organ
      - [versions 1-6], 6 audiocassettes (Box 61)
      - [version 7], 3 audiocassettes digital audio tapes (Box 61)
      - [version 8], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [version 9], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 10 1/2" (Box 76)
    - Sphaera, for piano and computer generated four-channel tape
      - [versions 1-3], 3 audiocassettes (Box 61)
      - [version 4], 1 audiocassettes digital audio tapes (Box 61)
      - [version 5], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 6], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 7], 1 audiocassettes (Box 60)
      - [versions 8-12], 6 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 71)
        (tape part for performance)
      - [version 13-14], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 71)
    - [composition for Sports Illustrated film: Fun and Games and Deeper Passions], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 10 1/2" (Box 76)
    - Stipendium Peccati, for organ, piano and percussion
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 61)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [versions 3-7], 5 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 71)
      - [version 8], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
      - [versions 9-10], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [version 11], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
      - [version 12], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
    - Sweet Sixteenths: a classy rag for piano
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
    - Symphony for Organ, with percussion (or pre-recorded tape)
      - [versions 1-4], 3 audiocassettes (Box 61)
      - [version 5], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 10 1/2" (Box 76)
    - Take That, for 4 drummers with 16 drums
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 61)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 3], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 71)
      - [version 4], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
    - Take Up the Song, for mixed choir, soprano solo and piano
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 61)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
      - [version 3], 1 audiocassettes (Box 59)
    - That Saxophone Rag (arrangement)
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 61)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
    - That Sinking Feeling (morceau de concours), 1 audiocassettes (Box 61)
    - Three New Chestnuts, for two harpsichords
      - [version 1], 2 audiocassettes (Box 61)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 71)
    - Three Novelty Rags, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
      (taped with Grand Sonata in Rag)
    - Three Original Rags, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
    - Tic: a spectacle for two groups of performers, soloist, films, and tape
      - [versions 1-2], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 71)
      - [versions 3-4], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 71)
        (complete performance)
      - [version 5], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
    - Two Pieces for Nine Instruments
      - [version 1], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 69)
        ("Quick Getaway" only, taped with Foils)
      - [version 3], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 70)
    - Valley of Fire for sax quartet and organ
      - [versions 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 61)
    - Whistler: Three Nocturnes, 1 audiocassettes (Box 61)
    - [Untitled, with three movements] (see Marcia Funebre) (Box 61)
    - Unidentified and fragments
      - Cassettes and DATs, 16 audiocassettes; 2 audiocassettes digital audio tapes (Box 61)
      - Reel-reel tape, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
  - William Albright Published Material
    - Compact Discs (with WA music and/or WA performances)
      - A Box of Views, Sierra Wind Quintet: Works by American Composers William Albright, Barney Childs, Alvin Etler, Mel Powell 1989 (Box 77)
      - Classical/Jazz: Michael Arnowitt, piano 1990 (Box 77)
      - The Complete Rags of Scott Joplin: William Albright, piano 1990 (Box 77)
      - Douglas Reed Plays the C.B. Fisk Organ Opus 98 1997 (Box 77)
      - Flights of Fancy: Premiere Recordings of New Music for Organ by Albright, Bielawa and Decker, Pamela Decker, organ 1994 (Box 77)
      - Marches, Waltzes & Rags of Scott Joplin: William Albright, piano 1993 (Box 77)
      - Organbook I & II by William Albright, David Craighead, organist 1988 (Box 77)
      - The Piano Music of William Albright, Thomas Warburton, piano, 1981 (1996) (Box 77)
      - Ragtime: Scott Joplin: Collaborative Rags, James P. Johnson: Stride Pieces, 1975 (1981, 1984 1995) (Box 77)
      - The Symphonic Jazz of James P. Johnson: Fascination, April in Harlem, Yamekraw, William Albright, Piano 1986 (Box 77)
      - William Albright: Music for Organ and Harpsichord, Performed by Douglas Reed, organ and harpsichord 1991 (Box 77)
      - American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters Award Record: Paul Chihara: Missa Carminum Brevis, Magnificat, Ave Maria; C. Curtis-Smith: Masquerades; William Albright, organ 1979 (Box 77)
      - Dean Sanders, Pianist, Plays William Albright, Burrill Phillips, John Watts undated (Box 77)
      - New Music for Organ: William Bolcom, Black Host, William Albright, Organbook II, William Albright, organ with Sidney Hodkinson, percussion 1971 (Box 77)
      - The Piano Music of William Albright, Thomas Warburton, piano 1981 (Box 77)
      - Ragtime Back to Back, James P. Johnson: Stride Pieces, William Albright, piano; Scott Joplin: Collaborative Rags, William Bolcom, piano 1981 (Box 77)
      - Re:Percussions: The University of Michigan Percussion Ensemble Conducted by Charles Owen 1984 (Box 77)
      - Sounds of Nations: Dr. William Haller at the Delaware Organ of the United Nations Parish Holy Family Church 1975 (Box 77)
      - Sydney Hodkinson: Megalith Trilogy, William Albright, organ 1976 (Box 77)
      - William Albright: Organbook, Juba, Pneuma circa 1970 (Box 77)
  - William Albright Performances
    - Carillon Improv, 1 audiocassettes (Box 61)
    - Music Sundays at First Unitarian-Universalist Church of Ann Arbor), 6 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 71)
    - Piano, Organ and Ragtime, 2 audiocassettes (Box 61)
    - Piano, Organ and Ragtime
      - [versions 1-14], 14 audiocassettes (Box 62)
      - [version 15], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 71)
      - [version 16], 2 reel-to-reel audiotapes 10 1/2" (Box 76)
      - [version 17], 3 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
    - Various Composers, 9 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 71)
      (includes Albright performances of pieces by Bach, Bolcom, G. Cacioppo, Castiglioni, Curtis-Smith, Danforth, Dururfle, Handel, Hodkinson, Ives, Morris, Peck)
  - William Albright Lectures
    - "Church Music [That Doesn't Sound Like Church Music] ", 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 5" (Box 72)
    - "Concept of Time", 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 72)
    - "Desert Island Discs", 2 audiocassettes (Box 72)
    - Lecture for Society/Fellows, 1995, 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Lecture on Organ Music undated, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology/WGBH (Boston) 1987, 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - "New Organ Music", 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 72)
    - SECCA/WFDD 1992, 2 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - "Spirit", 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - "The Spirit of American Rhythm", 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 72)
    - "Three American Revolutionaries: Cage/Brant/Nancanow", 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Yeats Lecture, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
  - Other Composers/Performers
    - Abramsen, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Adams, [?], 3 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Adams, John, 5 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Adams, Richard, 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Ahlstrom, Albert, 5 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Aikman, James, 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Albert, [?], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 80)
      (taped with Hodkinson)
    - Albright, Sarah Ann (Kirk), 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
    - Alexander, Kathryn, 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Alston, Lettie, 2 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Amlin, Martin, 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Anderson, Claudia, 2 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Andriessen, Louis, 2 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Angell, Michael, 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Arasimowicz, George, 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Armstrong, John, 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Ashley, [?] (Box 79)
      - [version 1], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 78)
    - Asia, Daniel, 2 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Asplin, David, 2 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Babbitt, Milton
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
        (taped with Martino)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
        (taped with Bassett)
    - Baker, Claude, 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Baldus, Ben, 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Ballard, [?], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 80)
      (taped with Bolcom)
    - Banfield, William, 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Bashaw, H., 1 audiocassettes (Box 67)
      (taped with Pichet)
    - Bass, Jeffery (performed by University of Michigan Chamber Choir), 1 audiocassettes (Box 62)
    - Bassett, Leslie
      - [versions 1-4], 3 audiocassettes (Box 62)
      - [version 5], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 79)
      - [version 6], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 80)
    - Bates, [?], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 81)
      (taped with G.B. Wilson)
    - Bates, David S., 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 72)
    - Beavers, Kevin, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Becker, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Beckwith, John], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
      (taped with Burke)
    - Beerman, Burton, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 81)
      (taped with Winkler)
    - Ben-Amots, Ofer, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Benjamin, George, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Benjamin, Steven, 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 72)
    - Bermel, Derek), 3 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Biggs, Hayes, 2 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Billmeyer, Dean, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Bithova, Eva, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
      (taped with Mott)
    - Boelter, Karl, 2 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Bolcom, William
      - [versions 1-2], 2 audiocassettes (Box 63)
      - [version 3], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 5" (Box 79)
      - [version 4], 3 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 80)
      - [version 6], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 80)
        (taped with Finney)
    - Bourland, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Bovet, Guy, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Branca, Glenn
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 64)
        (taped with M. Davies)
    - Bronson, William, 1 audiocassettes (Box 66)
      (taped with Maslanka)
    - Bruce, Neely), 3 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Buchman, Konrad, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Burke, John
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
      - [version 2], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 80)
    - Burton, Deborah, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Cacioppo, Curt, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Cacioppo, George
      - [versions 1-4], 3 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 72)
      - [version 5], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 5" (Box 80)
    - Campanelli, R., 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Campbell, Michael, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Carpenter, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Castiglioni, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Caviani, Laura, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Celona, John, 1 audiocassettes (Box 68)
      (taped with Smalley)
    - Chambers, Evan, 11 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Chatman, [?], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 80)
    - Chang, Dorothy, 2 audiocassettes (Box 80)
    - Changqun, [?], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Cherney, Brian, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Child, Peter, 2 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Class, Kevin, 2 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Clement, [?], 1 reel-to-reel audiotapes 7" (Box 80)
    - Colgrass, M
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
        (taped with Druckman)
    - Contreras, Jesus, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Corigliano, John
      - [version 1], 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
      - [version 2], 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
        (taped with Hamel)
    - Corta, John, 1 audiocassettes (Box 65)
    - Costinescu, Gheorghe, 1 audiocassettes (Box 63)
    - Cummings, Conrad, 2 audiocassettes (Box 63)